Jack Curtin

About

Throughout my life I have been guided by my passions for storytelling and music. Connecting with others driven by the same spirit keeps me motivated and inspired. I'm ready to throw myself full-force into my next role, contributing strong musical knowledge, sales experience, and an eagerness to collaborate and connect.

Contact

T: (803) 429-5387

jackcurtin94@gmail.com www.thoroughlybad.com

2527 N Monticello Ave Apt 2R Chicago, IL 60647



Experience

Move-tastic!

03/2020 - Present

IT Technician / Customer Service Representative
Regularly performed maintenance on tablets and other
technology devices used in the field, as well as tracked and
optimized computer and network health in the office. Drafted
personalized estimates based on client-provided information.
Managed scheduling clients and staffing the movers, tailoring
crews that would best fit the client's needs. Worked with
clients to settle any damage claims opened up after their
move. Assisted potential clients through email or phone
correspondence with any inquiries about the company's
services, as well as made any adjustments for current clients.

Reckless Records

10/2017 - 3/2020

Floor Manager / Used Product Buyer

Worked with other employees in determining a fair price to offer the seller that corresponds with our used product margin. Dealt closely with customers when paying them out and explaining our process of purchasing . As floor manager, responsibilities included opening/closing the store each shift, counting the money, and filling out the necessary paperwork. Also handled retail and customer service responsibilities.

Big Star Chicago

03/2017 - 12/2018

Food Runner

Delivered food in a fast-paced work environment centered around working with a large team to provide excellent and efficient service. Developed a deep knowledge and understanding of an ever-rotating menu to support the restaurant's reputation for unique tacos and whiskey.

Loyola University ITS

05/2014 - 01/2017

Network Security Intern / Help Desk Technician Worked with students to troubleshoot network connection issues and solve problems they were having with their personal devices. Assisted in the maintenance of ethernet and cable ports across campus.



Education

Loyola University Chicago Bachelor's in Film and Digital Media

Graduated May 2017

Universidad Alberto Huertado Studied abroad in Santiago, Chile Documentary Production

Summer 2016



Skills

Software Experience

- Proficiency of Adobe Premiere, Audition, & G-Suite programs
- Adept Knowledge of Adobe Photoshop & In Design
- · Introductory knowledge of HTML, CSS, and Javascript

Independent Projects & Passions

- · Self-produced documentaries, short films, photography, and music
- · Available to view at thoroughlybad.com/jackcurtin